<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>http://localhost:4000</id>
    <title>VIBELUV Expert Adult Product Guides &amp; Sex Tips</title>
    <updated>2025-11-28T19:16:47.532Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <link rel="self" href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>This site is a blog site under VIBELUV, aiming to share knowledge, experience and insights about adult products and sex.</subtitle>
    <logo>http://localhost:4000/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>http://localhost:4000/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2025, VIBELUV Expert Adult Product Guides &amp; Sex Tips</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips for men and women having sex for the first time (what you should be aware of when having sex for the first time).]]></title>
        <id>http://localhost:4000/post/tips-for-men-and-women-having-sex-for-the-first-time-what-you-should-be-aware-of-when-having-sex-for-the-first-time/</id>
        <link href="http://localhost:4000/post/tips-for-men-and-women-having-sex-for-the-first-time-what-you-should-be-aware-of-when-having-sex-for-the-first-time/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-08-13T16:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>For many young boys and girls in their prime, a lack of knowledge about the sexes can result in lifelong regrets.<br>
Many children ask at an early age: Where did I come from? Most parents will not tell their children that they are the result of sex between mom and dad, the sperm and egg combine to fertilize the egg and develop slowly; they will not tell their children what condoms are and what they do; they will not tell their sons not to have sex if they cannot be responsible for her and really love her...<br>
They will only tell their children to protect themselves when they have a boyfriend, but how? Parents avoid talking about it.</p>
<p>Husband and wife life is not something unseemly, the fear is that you meet someone and hurt yourself, so women need to do the following things when they have sex with their partner for the first time:<br>
Good living habits: reasonable diet, good living habits, no alcohol and no smoking, stay away from drugs.</p>
<p>sexual organ hygiene: women are more susceptible to infection than boys, wash before each couple's life to prevent infectious diseases of the female genitourinary system, and wash afterwards.<br>
Reasonable arrangement of time, frequency and timing of conjugal life according to the specific conditions of both husband and wife; women should pay attention to the hygiene of conjugal life during menstruation, pregnancy, breastfeeding and menopause; those with heart, lung, liver, kidney and other important organs not functioning properly or those who are suffering from hypertension, arteriosclerosis and other serious illnesses should be guided by a physician to have conjugal life.<br>
Contraception: Couples of childbearing age who no longer wish to have children or who do not wish to have children for the time being should adopt effective contraceptive measures suitable for both couples to avoid unwanted pregnancies. (Condoms are preferred, but attention should be paid to the correct use; or oral contraceptive pills and other methods, irresponsible also do not take contraceptive measures of scum or let him bypass ~ women can remember to self-protection,)<br>
Prevention of sexually transmitted diseases: to eliminate promiscuity is the most effective measure to prevent sexually transmitted diseases, one of the husband and wife suffers from sexually transmitted diseases, should be husband and wife together for treatment, recommended the use of condoms during the period of illness, to prevent infections between husband and wife.<br>
with their own love for the first time should belong to a relatively happy thing, do not be to please the partner, experience freshness to do, so the mind must be good, they can be in the textbook or formal medical website to learn about the relevant knowledge, it is best to two people can communicate and discuss, in the most difficult to talk about our views on the things we contain the most profound understanding of the world and life. The process of any uncomfortable situation should be timely raised!<br>
Sex education is related to a person's life, different ages and different life situations should receive relevant education, the focus of childhood is to guide the child's correct attitude to help the child to develop a correct gender self-identification and awareness of gender roles, and for adolescent girls, the significance of this kind of education is particularly significant. For adolescent girls, this kind of education is particularly significant, for example, to correctly recognize normal physiological phenomena such as physiological period; in adulthood, this kind of education is mainly to help both spouses to establish a happy and harmonious conjugal life.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Couples can not live five kinds of manifestations - men and women to know.]]></title>
        <id>http://localhost:4000/post/couples-can-not-live-five-kinds-of-manifestations-men-and-women-to-know/</id>
        <link href="http://localhost:4000/post/couples-can-not-live-five-kinds-of-manifestations-men-and-women-to-know/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-08-10T16:47:31.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Between husband and wife, if you can't go on, then there are five manifestations, that is quite obvious, between the two people, as long as the five situations, go on without any meaning; see husband and wife can't go on five manifestations.</p>
<p>Married life, every couple, in just married, are thinking to be with each other, with each other for life, and keep each other for life; but the marriage road, not always smooth sailing, there are a lot of times, will always be because of some things, between the two, there is a contradiction, produced a rift; and there are some cases, and will not make the husband and wife, the feelings of all the rupture; however, there are some cases, it will certainly make the Between two people, can not go on; two people can not go on, some have some very obvious performance; so couples can not go on five kinds of performance is which?</p>
<p>First, not only every day noise, and also moved the hand</p>
<p>In the married life, between husband and wife, because from childhood to adulthood, two people grow up in different environments, the idea is not the same, so in the treatment of a matter of opinion will not be the same, will not be unanimous; this is in fact very normal, but to understand each other, mutual tolerance; if the couple together, not only every day noisy, and also will be hands to hit, play the rough behavior, then such a husband and wife, it is impossible to go how much! Far; because the woman's heart, the bottom of the sea needle, there is no that a woman, can accept to be their loved ones, scolding every day; because now a lot of women, from childhood are pampered by their parents grew up, and how to accept, their own men's merciless treatment.</p>
<p>Second, long-term separation, there is no normal conjugal life</p>
<p>Husband and wife together for a lifetime, maintaining the bond of affection, that is, couples must live a normal married life; people are flesh and blood people, need to get energy release; if two people living apart for a long time, do not get energy release; natural heart, it will be particularly uncomfortable, it will be very unhappy; there are a lot of times, will also be suffocated to disease; so such a situation, the husband and wife days to the other side, it is not possible to go! How far; in the couple's life, if the two people can not get physical satisfaction, one day, the two people will go their own way, become strangers; this is the husband and wife life on the road, the most helpless thing.</p>
<p>Third, never communicate, endless cold war</p>
<p>In married life, there are many things between husband and wife, that is the need to communicate, to be able to get a solution; if two people together, there are a lot of things that can not be satisfactorily dealt with, then naturally can not be solved; between the two people, always endless cold war, then the two people live in the world, that is a particularly helpless thing; if two people together, have reached the step of the If two people together, have reached the step of no words, then with a stranger there is no difference; in this case, divorce is only a matter of time.</p>
<p>Fourth, one of the people outside the marriage really love someone else</p>
<p>True love is deep-rooted, is unable to self-control; a person's heart, as long as truly in love with a person, then the other party is all everything, is all, is the world; a person's heart, with the existence of another person, then no matter for each other, how much to pay, are all willing things; between husband and wife, if one of them, outside of marriage, really in love with a person, then such a Marriage, it must not go far; because the true love of the people, will be for the people outside the marriage, pay for all of their own everything, hand over their own a true heart; at this time, the dumping of the family, that is a very normal thing; the two go their own way, that is a matter of course.</p>
<p>Fifth, the other side of things, show hand bystanders</p>
<p>Couples live together, that is a whole; two people's things, that are a family of things; but if couples live together, the man's things, is the man's things, the woman's things, is the woman's things, then such couples, live together, will not last long; because of their own beloved, are show hand bystanders, then in the future of life, and what kind of a Meaning; two people have divided each other, treat each other as strangers; then such a couple life, there is no meaning.</p>
<p>Husband and wife can not go on five performance is the most typical, but there are also many cases, between husband and wife, can not go on; but no matter how, since there is a chance to become a husband and wife, should be caring for each other, mutual understanding; have a chance to be together, have to cherish; management of the marriage, that is the need to pay attention to the method; but can not tolerate, but is the most critical point; want to live a lifetime of happy life, then you have to be Endure each other; good day is run out, and bad day is also their own hands destroyed; so all couples, should be to walk and cherish.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Couples with poor quality of sex life may try to play 4 kinds of games.]]></title>
        <id>http://localhost:4000/post/couples-with-poor-quality-of-sex-life-may-try-to-play-4-kinds-of-games/</id>
        <link href="http://localhost:4000/post/couples-with-poor-quality-of-sex-life-may-try-to-play-4-kinds-of-games/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-08-07T16:46:48.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>What should couples do if they have a low quality sex life? It has been found that before the start of a couple's sex life, some room games help to improve the quality of sex life, and keep sex life fresh. This is undoubtedly a good catalyst for the couple's relationship. Here are a few kinds of room games for you to take a look.</p>
<p>First, baby games</p>
<p>Couples can pretend to be children, very &quot;curious&quot; to see each other's bodies and breasts. Can also be like a baby like murmuring, stimulate each other's mother love or father love. Husbands can act like sons, lying in their wives' arms, &quot;acting out, being bad and wild&quot;, tweaking and sucking on their wives' nipples. For the childless wife, her husband's suckling melts her desire for a future child into tenderness for him. For wives who have children, the gentle touch of her husband's lips evokes in her mind all the happy memories of feeding her children in the past.</p>
<p>Second, animal games</p>
<p>Couples imitate animal play, play, sexual intercourse action, take turns acting to each other to see, thereby causing each other's laughter, relaxation due to other things and taut nerves, to maintain a relaxed, happy and humorous state of mind. 1973 Changsha Mawangdui No. 3 Han Tomb unearthed the &quot;together yin and yang&quot; book, discusses the ten kinds of imitation of animal play sexual intercourse action, and called the &quot;ten sections and called it &quot;Ten Sections&quot;. These ten sections are the specific application of ancient bionics in the room life. It argues that these ten actions can be used both to playfully tease, but also to imitate its posture * intercourse.</p>
<p>Third, naked and fantasy games</p>
<p>Couples naked all over, either in the accompaniment of soft romantic music, dancing sexy dance. Either embracing each other and lying down talking about love, touching each other's bodies. Either have a game of chess, lose a game to take off a piece of clothing. Can also be in the soft light, prepare some food and wine, while eating and drinking and chatting, chatting when don't let the eyes idle. When needed, ruffle the ends of her hair for her, help him wipe away the remaining crumbs of food on his lips. Maybe it's just a night of pure talk, or maybe it's a night of lingering.</p>
<p>Four, sex game notes</p>
<p>Couples doing sex games, pay attention to one thing: do not do before and in the middle of thinking about it to lead to sexual intercourse activities. Because once this kind of psychology, do up will be distracted, want to end as soon as possible sex games, so that the other party has a kind of feeling of being used. Sex games can be * intercourse &quot;prelude&quot;, can also be a sexual activity &quot;solo&quot;. Both partners should focus on the emotional experience of pleasure and intimacy rather than on whether it will lead to intercourse. When one party has no desire to have sex, the other party should take it as a unique sexual experience, can not force each other; when both sides of the emotional high, sexual intercourse will be water to the end. In short, everything should go with the flow, only to emphasize the process rather than the end.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The woman is active and both parties are happy.]]></title>
        <id>http://localhost:4000/post/the-woman-is-active-and-both-parties-are-happy/</id>
        <link href="http://localhost:4000/post/the-woman-is-active-and-both-parties-are-happy/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-08-05T16:46:09.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>For a long time, women were set up as a passive animal. It was not until Lawrence wrote about women's desires in the name of Lady Chatterley that it was realized that women desire and are able to dominate even in the most essential and secretive of male-female relationships. At the same time, when women direct the sexual... Men tend to have more fun when women direct the &quot;main theme&quot; of sex. Recently, the American magazine Women's Health gave specific instructions on how women can make their partners &quot;oblivious&quot;.</p>
<p>Tip #1: Let him enjoy - tease him with the most attractive dress and posture!</p>
<p>Explanation: Men are visual creatures, see their favorite woman flavorful, provocative and seductive look, the most can provoke his libido. If your husband's sexual interest is not high, you can wear a wide shirt, or add a pair of sexy stockings and high-heeled shoes, and then sit on the bed, which is thirsty posture, conveying the signal of desire.</p>
<p>Tip #2: Make him &quot;stand up&quot; - wake him up with your deft fingers!</p>
<p>Explanation: Men also like to be touched and caressed, and they are happy to see their wives' fingers running over their bodies. If he has a weak erection, his wife can pour some massage oil on her hands and gently caress her partner's sensitive areas, such as the penis, pubic area, and the penis.... Penis, scrotum... Sac, etc.</p>
<p>The third trick: rotate around the track - take the male lower female position when more twisting their bodies to achieve orgasm</p>
<p>Explanation: In order for the male's sexual... Desire is fully aroused, while increasing the pressure on the clitoris... Clitoris and G-spot stimulation. Points of stimulation, women can be in the sex... Twist herself in an elliptical trajectory during sex. The ... Penis in the process of pumping, women can also slightly probe backward to make the stimulation more intense.</p>
<p>Tip #4: Adjust the angle appropriately - rear entry is the most seductive</p>
<p>Interpretation: the biggest advantage of this move is to make the woman's arched buttocks more attractive, while at the same time fully stimulating the G... Point. Women can kneel on the edge of the bed and let their husbands stand behind them, puckering their buttocks as high as possible.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eight tips for couples to experience the "sex" fun of intercourse.]]></title>
        <id>http://localhost:4000/post/eight-tips-for-couples-to-experience-the-sex-fun-of-intercourse/</id>
        <link href="http://localhost:4000/post/eight-tips-for-couples-to-experience-the-sex-fun-of-intercourse/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-08-04T16:44:53.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Satisfaction is the highest state of affairs, both men and women enjoy that peak moment. But focus too much energy on the &quot;must meet&quot; goal, but will affect the pleasure. Recently, American and French sexologists have come up with new rules for sexual fulfillment to help partners enjoy the pleasure.</p>
<p>Chinese medicine prescription: this with the kidney to give strength</p>
<p>Ingredients: 1 gram of sea ginseng, 8 wolfberries.</p>
<p>How to use: Add both ingredients into one cup, soak in boiling water for 5 minutes and drink. This is a famous Chinese medicine recipe for men. This recipe must use sea ginseng, ordinary ginseng does not have this effect. The Chinese wolfberries are large, full and uniform in color.</p>
<p>Eight tips to make love more sexual happiness</p>
<p>1, eliminate the time difference of 12~36 minutes.</p>
<p>Men on average need about 6~8 minutes to reach sexual satisfaction, women usually need 20~40 minutes, there is a time difference of about 12~36 minutes between the two. The partner should be aware of this time difference and shorten it by more physical caresses.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>Carry out foreplay outside the bedroom.</li>
</ol>
<p>Foreplay must not be optional, but a &quot;requirement&quot;. It is not limited to the physical aspects of sexual contact, in addition to some explicit sexual expression, send erotic text messages, say compliments and mutual massage can better stimulate the partner's desire.</p>
<p>3, fast meet before stopping.</p>
<p>Between partners can be used &quot;to escape&quot; method to extend the time of intercourse, that is, almost reached sexual satisfaction when the abrupt end, start again. It should be remembered that the slightly flawed intercourse can not be transformed overnight, both sides must persistently adhere to the exercise and practice, in order to learn to stay on the bed for a longer period of time.</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>Always use lubricant.</li>
</ol>
<p>Every couple can benefit from using lubricant: it helps with lubrication, reduces pain, and increases eroticism. ...... Lubricant should be a standard, kept handy.</p>
<ol start="5">
<li>Keeping in a good mood helps fulfillment.</li>
</ol>
<p>Surveys have shown that it is easier to achieve fulfillment is those who are young, have a harmonious relationship in their marriage overall, and are in a relaxed and happy mood. When the mind is good, happy life, couples can achieve double satisfaction of body and mind during intercourse --- this is the supreme state of intercourse, not only what women seek, men are also the same. To get such satisfaction, maintain a happy mood, create a comfortable room environment, exchange room feeling are very important.</p>
<p>6, don't exclude erotic toys.</p>
<p>For some couples, it is true that the initial use of sex toys is a bit awkward and strange, but this is just a process of sexual improvement. If you are not accustomed to vibrators and other toys, you can choose to have floating condoms to increase the fun.</p>
<p>7, Don't stay away from masturbation.</p>
<p>Although it's harder for women to achieve fulfillment, exploring your body will make a difference. Masturbation is a shortcut to fulfillment. The survey found that half of the women through masturbation to achieve sexual satisfaction for the first time in their lives, couples mutual masturbation is also a good way.</p>
<p>8, multiple satisfaction is not difficult.</p>
<p>Women should not period (refers to the end of an intercourse to the body state and can start the next intercourse between the necessary interval time) is shorter than men, so you can experience multiple satisfaction. Therefore, men can first satisfy women through caressing, etc., and then reach the peak together.</p>
<p>Eat a healthy diet for good kidneys</p>
<p>Hometown Fried Earth Squid</p>
<p>The earth squid into the addition of alkali water soaking hair; cloud ear water hair wash; bamboo shoots shell wash clean sliced; onion wash clean to remove the old skin sliced; squash wash clean to remove the pith sliced; ginger wash clean sliced; garlic peeled and washed clean chopped into a garlic paste; starch and water to mix into the wet starch about 10 grams of boiling pot of oil, will be the earth squid put to pull the oil to only cooked, dumped in the strainer? Strain the oil. Put the pot back on the stove, put ginger, garlic, wet cloud ear, loofah, onions, bamboo shoots in the pot, splash into the wine, splash into the boiling two soup 10 ml, add the earth squid pulled through the oil, with the gravy soup 30 ml, wet cornstarch, pepper, and well as thickening, plus 5 grams of oil on the tail of the packet to stir fry on the plate will be completed.</p>
<p>Fried Amaranth</p>
<p>Amaranth roots and old leaves removed and washed, cut into 3 cm long sections, into the boiling water pot blanch and then fished out, drained; garlic, ginger are minced. Pan set on high heat, put salad oil, burned to 60% hot, under the ginger, garlic stir incense, and then into the amaranth, add salt, monosodium glutamate stir-fry evenly, dripping sesame oil, out of the pan can be loaded on the plate.</p>
<p>Stir Fried Mushroom with Green Pepper</p>
<p>Wash green peppers and break them into pieces. Tear the mushrooms into strips, blanch, cool and dry. Stir frying pan with appropriate amount of vegetable oil, add green peppers and stir-fry for two minutes over high heat. Add the mushrooms and stir-fry. Cook soy sauce, cooking wine and salt. Put two grams of starch in a small bowl, moderate amount of water, pour into the pan thickening, put monosodium glutamate, out of the pan on the plate.</p>
<p>Broccoli fried meat</p>
<p>Wash broccoli, blanch with boiling water, shred or slice pork. Heat oil in a pan, stir fry chopped ginger and garlic, stir fry chopped pork until brown. Add broccoli and stir-fry for 1 minute. Add salt, monosodium glutamate, soy sauce and oil and stir-fry well.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are the techniques for making love?]]></title>
        <id>http://localhost:4000/post/what-are-the-techniques-for-making-love/</id>
        <link href="http://localhost:4000/post/what-are-the-techniques-for-making-love/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-08-03T16:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The highest state of lovemaking is not only comfortable, but also to achieve orgasm. If you can master a little lovemaking skills, it will certainly be able to add points to the lovemaking experience, to help each other to release the desire to enjoy sexual pleasure.</p>
<p>So, what are the techniques of lovemaking?</p>
<p>1, increase the kissing skills, arousing sexual desire</p>
<p>In fact, the sensitivity of the lips is second only to the female clitoris, if you make love to incorporate some kissing skills, you can give both sides to bring a better, exciting experience.</p>
<p>(1) two lips touch: two people in the lips between the edge of the slide each other, as in the capture is falling from the spoon pudding, this feeling is particularly wonderful.</p>
<p>(2) Transporting the tongue method: the tissues under the tongue are very sensitive, try to use the tip of the teasing tongue to explore the highest point of eroticism, with kisses to express your endless passion.</p>
<p>(3) full of love and light bite: this is a more exciting kissing method, you can use your teeth to bite each other's lips, but the strength should be grasped, do not force, so as not to bite.</p>
<p>(4) sucking: you can first gently suck each other's lips, inhaling and sucking out each other's moist lips can especially stimulate sexual desire, and then slowly suck each other's tongue.</p>
<p>2, the use of erotic products to improve the level of pleasure</p>
<p>Try to use erotic products, such as erotic lingerie, threaded condoms, etc., can improve the excitement and stimulation of lovemaking to a certain extent. A survey shows that in Tel Aviv, many women will go to the sex store in pairs to buy things, female mini oscillator has become their &quot;bosom friend&quot;. The use of sex toys, slight and sexy teasing partner, can arouse his &quot;animal&quot; so that both sides better orgasm.</p>
<p>3, skillfully stimulate the sex sensitive area, get an orgasm</p>
<p>You can touch your own or your partner's sex sensitive areas to slowly ignite sexual desire, this touch can stop from time to time, and sometimes repeated, in order to skillfully evoke orgasm. Especially with its gentle action to touch the most sensitive parts of the female, that is, the clitoris, can often make women faster to reach orgasm.</p>
<p>4, dare to try a variety of positions, sustained passion</p>
<p>A survey by Women's Health magazine found that the source of Brazilian passion lies in the spirit of exploration and innovation in sex: 77% of people will try new sex positions or ways. The woman-on-top position is one that makes it easier for women to reach orgasm because it allows them to control the process of lovemaking, such as the depth of penile penetration and the degree of clitoral stimulation, in order to maximize sexual stimulation.</p>
<p>5, take the initiative to put forward the demand, tacit cooperation</p>
<p>Make love is not a person's thing, the two in-depth communication, take the initiative to put forward the needs of the more tacit cooperation. Especially in the process of making love, actively take the initiative to each other to pass their own preferences and sensitive parts of the information, can help both sides better into the state. A survey of 14,840 Israeli women showed that 72% of the people in a recent sexual climax, and 71% of people know how to raise the need for sex. It is evident that pleasure and sexual satisfaction can be maximized with in-depth communication and tacit cooperation between partners.</p>
<p>Reference:<br>
Qianlong. Six kissing skills[J]. Hunan Agricultural Machinery, 2004(3):32-32.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cold Fact: 10 Benefits of Showering Together as a Couple?]]></title>
        <id>http://localhost:4000/post/cold-fact-10-benefits-of-showering-together-as-a-couple/</id>
        <link href="http://localhost:4000/post/cold-fact-10-benefits-of-showering-together-as-a-couple/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-08-02T16:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>There is a way to continue to deal with disharmony in the family, no matter what the problem is. The way is to take a bath with your partner. The benefits of bathing together as a couple have been studied by many scientists and the results obtained are that there are many benefits of bathing together with the couple. Here are some of the benefits we show you.</p>
<p>Stress Relief.</p>
<p>Stress is surprisingly the biggest killer in the history of human health. Taking a bath with your loved ones can ease the nerves.</p>
<p>Body Care</p>
<p>Often, when you bathe alone, the back of your body will be hard to reach for cleaning. By sharing a bathroom, you will be able to clean the back of your body and your body will be well maintained.</p>
<p>Increased confidence</p>
<p>By taking a bath together, your emotional bond with your partner will increase and so you will be very confident that you will be able to overcome the problems that arise in your family life.</p>
<p>Good for heart health</p>
<p>If you soak in warm water while bathing, then you will get additional benefits apart from your growing harmony. Namely, your heart health will be better because your blood circulation is smoother due to the warm water.</p>
<p>Calms the nerves</p>
<p>Similar to making love, bathing with your partner can also calm the nerves.</p>
<p>Relieves headaches</p>
<p>A recent study found the fact that there is a correlation between bathing with your partner and headache attacks. This is due to the fact that during showering together, there is physical contact accompanied by splashing water, causing a stimulation that can calm the tension in the head and make the headache pain subside.</p>
<p>Builds intimacy and sensuality</p>
<p>Taking a bath with your partner is the same as cuddling in bed. By showering together, it's as if you and your partner are sharing everything together. In this way, your relationship with your partner will become more intimate and increase from the sexiness aspect.</p>
<p>Create more harmonious communication</p>
<p>Communication can also be accomplished, including communicating problems that arise in your relationship. The atmosphere of the bathroom and the splash of water will help your mind and your partner to keep up with the problems more calmly and positively.</p>
<p>Increased Happiness</p>
<p>Taking a shower with your partner may sound sexy. But by doing these activities, you will feel the pleasure that makes you addicted.</p>
<p>Love grows stronger</p>
<p>The atmosphere in the bathroom is just two people, splashing or soaking in water. This atmosphere will make your love and your partner's feelings sprout again.</p>
<p>Be more discreet<br>
The benefits of showering together as a couple will make you happy, and usually, this can also be apricot love foreplay. If you and your partner are having apricot sex in the bathroom, then you should be extra careful because the bathroom is an unsuitable location for apricot sex because of soap or mold.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's wrong with having sex that hurts down there?]]></title>
        <id>http://localhost:4000/post/whats-wrong-with-having-sex-that-hurts-down-there/</id>
        <link href="http://localhost:4000/post/whats-wrong-with-having-sex-that-hurts-down-there/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-08-01T16:42:11.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>There are many reasons for pain down there when having sex, the common ones are too much force or improper posture in coitus, vaginitis, endometriosis, etc. It can also be caused when a man suffers from prepuce glans dermatitis, prostatitis, epididymitis.</p>
<p>Excessive force or improper posture during coitus</p>
<p>If the preparation of foreplay is insufficient, the female vagina lacks expansion and lubrication, at this time, if the male partner is too hard or improper posture, frictional pain is likely to occur, and even lead to their own foreskin laceration, for women can lead to damage to the vaginal opening or mucous membranes, the vaginal opening can have a burning pain sensation. Especially when women have intercourse for the first time, if the posture and force are not appropriate, it can lead to vaginal soft tissue damage or hymen damage.</p>
<p>Vaginitis</p>
<p>If you suffer from trichomonas vaginitis, vulvovaginal candidiasis or atrophic vaginitis, the vaginal mucosa due to inflammation stimulation appears congested or even erosion, at this time, coitus will be below the pain, but also accompanied by vulvar itching, leukorrhea and other uncomfortable symptoms.</p>
<p>Endometriosis</p>
<p>If you suffer from endometriosis, when intercourse involves ectopic lesions or local adhesions, you may experience deep pain during intercourse, and the degree of pain is directly proportional to the number of times you have intercourse and the magnitude of your intercourse movements.</p>
<p>Other reproductive system diseases</p>
<p>For male patients, if there is foreskin glans, prostatitis, epididymitis, orchitis, penile cavernous sclerosis and other reproductive system diseases, the stimulation of the affected area during coitus can also appear as a symptom of pain in the lower body during coitus. Women with vaginal spasms, congenital vaginal deformities and other diseases may also experience pain at the vaginal opening during intercourse.</p>
<p>Other factors</p>
<p>In addition, when women enter menopause or menopause, due to the decrease in the secretion of relevant sex hormones, the vagina can be physiologically atrophic and dry, which will lead to male penile insertion and twitching obstacles, and is also prone to female sexual intercourse pain.</p>
<p>In short, if you are not sure what is going on when you have sex, it is best to go to a regular hospital in time to find out the cause of the disease and then treat the symptoms, so as to ensure that the &quot;sexual well-being&quot;.</p>
<p>References</p>
<p>[1] Ruan Nianchu. The first thing you need to do is to get rid of the pain in your eyes. 5 reasons[J]. The health of everyone,2021(14):52.</p>
<p>[2] Chen, J.. What is the reason for women's pain during sexual intercourse[J]. Family medicine,2021(09):46.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are some romantic kissing techniques? Take a look at seven romantic kissing styles.]]></title>
        <id>http://localhost:4000/post/what-are-some-romantic-kissing-techniques-take-a-look-at-seven-romantic-kissing-styles/</id>
        <link href="http://localhost:4000/post/what-are-some-romantic-kissing-techniques-take-a-look-at-seven-romantic-kissing-styles/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-08-01T16:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>What are some romantic kissing techniques? When it comes to couples, many of them start with kissing, and kissing is indeed an effective form of foreplay. So what are the romantic kissing techniques? The following small series will be introduced to you.</p>
<p>Kissing is an important means of regulating the life of a couple. What kind of kissing can increase the atmosphere? Quickly follow the small series to find out.</p>
<p>First, seven romantic ways of kissing</p>
<p>Blowing kissing. That is, when your lips touch, gently blow your breath into each other's mouth. This is a highly skilled way of kissing that can enhance the intimacy between two people. However, it is best not to use this method after drinking or smoking, so as not to transfer the odor to the other person and make him feel disgusted. In addition, do not blindly blow so that the other person can not breathe, otherwise it will also spoil the wonderful feeling of kissing.</p>
<p>Spiral kissing. Stick your tongue into each other's mouth and keep rotating it. This method should only be used when the two people are in silent cooperation.</p>
<p>Deep Kissing. Stick your tongue deep into each other's mouths, even to the depths of the throat. This method is not suitable for people with too long a tongue, as it will come into contact with the other person's throat and may be inappropriately disgusting.</p>
<p>Sucking on the lips. Hold or suck on the other person's lips. Because the mucous membranes of a woman's lips are more fragile, men must be gentle when sucking and stop immediately when they see pain in the other person's expression.</p>
<p>Kissing the teeth. Gently lick the other person's teeth with the tip of your tongue. It's best not to consider each tooth or it will feel like a dental checkup.</p>
<p>Vacuum kissing. After the lips touch, try to absorb as much air as possible from the other person's mouth. This method of kissing must take into account the shape of the man's and woman's lips. If one lip is too big and the other too small, like a small dandelion covering a large sunflower, it doesn't achieve the effect of a vacuum, but it also makes one person feel uncomfortable.</p>
<p>French Kissing. The supreme technique of kissing is illegal kissing. Sex experts can't miss this move. When kissing, you should add more techniques to your tongue, such as gently probing into the other person's mouth with your tongue first, then gently licking the inside of her mouth to get the other person's tongue entangled.</p>
<p>Second, different kisses have different meanings</p>
<p>Although all seven of these kissing styles are mesmerizing, they have different meanings.</p>
<p>For example, French kissing and deep kissing represent endless exploration and deeper contact, so they fully unleash each other's passion and are best suited as an important part of foreplay. Blow kissing is a bit naughty and mischievous and is perfect for two people to try out while having fun. Kissing on the teeth is an option for the most intimate of lovers.</p>
<p>There are little taboos for everyone in the kissing process, and only a good kisser can win the heart of a lover.</p>
<p>First of all, it is necessary to respond. Some women will just stand when kissing, with their hands stiff and drooping. Their boyfriends are like kissing a piece of wood. Imagine how he would feel inside. Therefore, once you accept a kiss from the other person, you have to respond.</p>
<p>Secondly, fight a prepared battle. Some men always like to attack each other unexpectedly and are used to kissing so roughly that the woman becomes a helpless lamb. The occasional accident may be refreshing for women, but more often than not it makes them wonder: do men respect the need to kiss?</p>
<p>Finally, mutual respect. Both men and women must prepare themselves before kissing. If time permits, you can brush your teeth, rinse your mouth or chew gum. A fresh tone of voice is the first step to a successful kiss, it also gives a hint to the other person: I take our kiss very seriously.</p>
<p>Taboos of kissing for men and women</p>
<ol>
<li>Bad breath</li>
</ol>
<p>There is nothing worse for couples who have just fallen in love. If you have such a problem, check your stomach and mouth problems and, of course, the most urgent and effective method is mints. If you don't want to say SayGoodbye to each other, please keep your breath fresh oh!</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>Tongue kiss is too passionate</li>
</ol>
<p>Maybe your love for him (or his love for you) is difficult to hold yourself, too enthusiastic and active, but will scare each other step by step, remember to rush! Suggested reference to romantic French kissing.</p>
<p>3, too reserved</p>
<p>It's always good to keep some mystery, but it doesn't always fully apply to relationships. If you really like each other, please let each other feel your passionate response in the right atmosphere!</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>Too stiff</li>
</ol>
<p>The stupidest way to kiss is to just lift your lips and stand there stiff and aloof. How can he kiss you? It's awkward, but some girls are like that! Kissing is a time when two people can't help themselves when they're in love, so how can you be such a dull spoilsport?</p>
<ol start="5">
<li>No hands</li>
</ol>
<p>Have you ever noticed where two people put their hands when they kiss? Is it warm when your beloved caresses your face or gently stops your waist while kissing? If you really like each other, extend your hand at the right time.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do men like a woman to tease them?]]></title>
        <id>http://localhost:4000/post/how-do-men-like-a-woman-to-tease-them/</id>
        <link href="http://localhost:4000/post/how-do-men-like-a-woman-to-tease-them/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-07-31T16:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Couple life is an indispensable flavor of life, but now the pressure is relatively large, every day to work and life and busy, many young people are therefore ignored the couple life, and even so the couple life disharmony, resulting in both sides of the feelings of cracks, so it is very important to grasp the method of regulating the disharmony of the couple's life.</p>
<p>What should we do if our life is not harmonious?</p>
<p>1, learn to release pressure</p>
<p>If you are under great pressure for a long time, you will lose your libido because of the bad mood, which will lead to the occurrence of the disharmony of the couple's life in the long run. Therefore, whether it is a man or a woman, you have to learn to release the pressure, and all kinds of methods can be used, as long as it is suitable for you is the best, such as listening to music.</p>
<ol>
<li>Quit smoking and drinking</li>
</ol>
<p>Harmful substances in cigarettes and alcohol will not only harm the respiratory system and liver, but also the hormone secretion and psychological regulation will also have certain side effects, prompting both men and women to have a low libido, so people who have the habit of smoking and drinking should quit smoking and drinking in time.</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>Actively carry out physical examination</li>
</ol>
<p>The interest in married life is not mentioned, may also be due to health problems, such as gynecological diseases or male diseases, these diseases will not only make the body uncomfortable, but also make the body of a certain function decline, including sexual function, at this time, we should actively carry out physical examination, and targeted treatment.</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>Cultivate feelings</li>
</ol>
<p>No matter how strong feelings, will slowly fade with the passage of time, this change will also affect the harmony of married life, so usually to create some surprises for each other, or do more to promote the feelings of things that help, such as caring for each other, over time the couple's life will become more harmonious.</p>
<p>5, active sports</p>
<p>Exercise is a natural doctor, active sports, not only can make the physical quality of some enhancement, but also can make the immune system to improve, but also can help to release the pressure, so both men and women should be active sports, it is recommended that both sides of the sports together to enhance the relationship and promote the harmony of the couple's life have a great deal of help, after all, couples also need to have a strong physical quality of the basis of the life.</p>
<p>Warm tips</p>
<p>Harmony in married life will not only affect the relationship between the two sides, but also may affect the physical health and mental health, so we should actively improve the state of married life. First of all, to find the right way to help themselves to release the pressure, and secondly to quit smoking and drinking, in addition to actively carry out physical examination, and do some things to promote the feelings of help, in addition to regular exercise habits.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>